Lakshmi Narashimha Naidu Palacholla

Hyderabad, Telangana, India 🛮 murali.palacholla@gmail.com 🔲 +91 8179343678 🛅 www.linkedin.com/in/narasimha-palacholla

SUMMARY

As a mechanical engineer turned Salesforce developer with overall 3.10 years of experience out of 2.2 years relevant, I specialize in Apex, Aura, and LWC along with Sales, Service and Experience clouds to enhance corporate operations and customer experiences. My quick learning and collaborative skills enable me to deliver unique solutions to clients. I'm passionate about exploring new technologies to solve real–world problems and eager to expand my Salesforce expertise.

SKILLS

- $\cdot \ \, \text{Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SOSL, SOQL, Aura Lightening components, Apex, Triggers, Visual force, Lightning Web Components$
- · Soft Skills: Effective Time Management, Growth Oriented, Proactive Communication, Creative Problem Solving, Collaborative.

EXPERIENCE

Salesforce Developer

Seanergy Digital

February 2022 - June 2023, Hyderabad, TS

- · Developed, Implemented, and maintained Salesforce applications including object and field customization and data integration using Apex, Visualforce, Aura components, LWC, triggers, Asynchronous apex and Flows.
- \cdot Typical responsibilities include managing user accounts, user roles, profiles, and creating and customizing reports and dashboards using lightning web components in experience cloud.
- · Designed and Implemented custom solutions on the platform using Apex and Visualforce pages, Integrating with other systems.

Salesforce Developer

Farmsoul

July 2021 - February 2022, Hyderabad, TS

- · Managing user accounts, customize reports and dashboards to track performance in website using Apex and Aura components.
- Managing different Accounts with single login id in community portal and including contact information, purchasing history and preferences displayed in portal using Aura components.
- Reporting and analytics capabilities, allowing businesses to gain insights into their e-commerce performance, including sales, service and customer behavior.

Design Engineer

Reliability Engineering Industries

June 2019 - January 2021, Hyderabad, TS

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ As a design engineer dealt with mechanical seals production and research.
- \cdot Obtaining the information needed from clients in order to build a mechanical seal for pumps, reactors, and other mechanical equipment.
- · Creating individual 3D part models from the customer drawing details and making a 2D draft for respective 3D part models.
- Giving logical stock code for production purposes to that 2D draught, and then, in the last stage, producing an assembly draught from a 3D assembly model.

PROJECTS

DMG GO

Seanergy Digital • February 2022 - March 2023

- They provide transportation to customers like Amazon, FedEx, and other local delivery services. These companies need trucks and drivers to deliver their products. DMGgo provides them with trucks and drivers. The owners of these trucks and drivers can use a community portal to manage everything.
- · Implemented a system to manage the driver onboarding process and step van(promotion) driver operations.
- This likely includes developing customized modules within the Salesforce platform that allow for offer letter generation.
- · Integrating data from the experience drive portal using LWC and Aura components.
- · Sending Emails and notifications to users both in driver onboarding process and off boarding process.
- · Implemented custom dynamic dashboards and reports in experience portal using Lightning web components.
- \cdot Uploading documents of driver offer package letters using custom pdf documentation.

Farm soul

Farm soul Pvt. services Lmtd • July 2021 - January 2022

- · E-commerce company which provides Food and Beverage Services to premium gated customers.
- · Implemented login pages which includes multiple user login along with changing UI according to Admin and Production users respectively with help of aura components.
- · Implemented reports and dashboards of a product purchase, stock and selling in admin portal.

CERTIFICATIONS

· Salesforce Certified Administrator

Salesforce · 2023

· Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I

Salesforce · 2023

· Copado Salesforce DevOps Fundamentals 1

Copado Cummunity · 2023

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of Technology

Minor in Mechanical Engineering • GITAM University • Bengaluru • 2018 • 7.39

COURSEWORK

· Salesforce Administrator · Salesforce Platform Developer 1

Trailhead \cdot 2023